quiz = [
    {
        'name' : 'q1',
        'question' : 'A boolean is something that stores true or false values',
        'options' : [
            {'answer' : 'True', 'correct' : True},
            {'answer' : 'False', 'correct' : False}
        ]
    },

    {
        'name' : 'q2',
        'question' : 'The command to print a something to the terminal in python is "console.log()"',
        'options' : [
            {'answer' : 'True', 'correct' : False},
            {'answer' : 'False', 'correct' : True},
           
        ]
    },

    {
        'name' : 'q3',
        'question' : "The $ establishes that you're coding in jQuery",
        'options' : [
            {'answer' : 'True', 'correct' : True},
            {'answer' : 'False', 'correct' : False},
            
        ]
    },

    {
        'name' : 'q4',
        'question' : "In python 2.7 the code line to get user input is 'raw_input()'",
        'options' : [
            {'answer' : 'True', 'correct' : True},
            {'answer' : 'False', 'correct' : False},
            
        ]
    },
    {
        'name' : 'q5',
        'question' : "The logical operator && will evaluate a statement as true only if both expressions are true",
        'options' : [
            {'answer' : 'True', 'correct' : True},
            {'answer' : 'False', 'correct' : False},
            
        ]
    },
    {
        'name' : 'q6',
        'question' : " The equation (3*5)++ will evaluate to 18",
        'options' : [
            {'answer' : 'True', 'correct' : False},
            {'answer' : 'False', 'correct' : True},
            
        ]
    },
    {
        'name' : 'q7',
        'question' : "=! is used in JavaScript for something not true ",
        'options' : [
            {'answer' : 'True', 'correct' : False},
            {'answer' : 'False', 'correct' : True},
            
        ]
    },
    {
        'name' : 'q8',
        'question' : "Three equal signs are used for a strict evaluate",
        'options' : [
            {'answer' : 'True', 'correct' : True},
            {'answer' : 'False', 'correct' : False},
            
        ]
    },
    {
        'name' : 'q9',
        'question' : "Companies like Facebook, Google, and Youtube use Python",
        'options' : [
            {'answer' : 'True', 'correct' : True},
            {'answer' : 'False', 'correct' : False},
            
        ]
    },
    {
       'name' : 'q10',
        'question' : " 7 % 2 would evaluate as 3.5",
        'options' : [
            {'answer' : 'True', 'correct' : False},
            {'answer' : 'False', 'correct' : True},
            
        ]
    },
]
